[
    
{ 

    "question": "The blood is made up of what color?",
     "options": {
         "A": "Purple",
         "B": "Pink",
         "C": "Red",
         "D": "Yellow"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = C"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "What part of the body is used for seeing?",
     "options": {
         "A": "Head",
         "B": "Shoulder",
         "C": "Knee",
         "D": "Eyes"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = D"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "Which of the following is a state in Nigeria?",
     "options": {
         "A": "New York",
         "B": "Kwara",
         "C": "Algeria",
         "D": "Ghana"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = B"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "Mom and Dad are also known as ________",
     "options": {
         "A": "Parents",
         "B": "Guardians",
         "C": "Mentors",
         "D": "Producers"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = A"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "Your mother’s brother’s only brother-in-law is asleep on your couch. Who is asleep on your couch?",
     "options": {
         "A": "Your brother",
         "B": "Your cousin",
         "C": "Your Brother-in-law",
         "D": "Your Father"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = D"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "What colour will I mix to get orange?",
     "options": {
         "A": "White and Red",
         "B": "Green and Black",
         "C": "Red and Yellow",
         "D": "Blue and Purple"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = C"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "What will I do when  I am wearing my top?",
     "options": {
         "A": "Wear it through my legs",
         "B": "Wear over my head",
         "C": "Wear it inside out",
         "D": "Wear a wet top"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = B"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "If your house was on fire, what would you do first?",
     "options": {
         "A": "Allow yourself burn",
         "B": "Shout for help",
         "C": "Continue sleeping",
         "D": "Ignore the fire"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = B"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "What’s the world’s fastest animal?",
     "options": {
         "A": "Cheetah",
         "B": "Elephant",
         "C": "Ant",
         "D": "Bird"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = A"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "Birds lay what?",
     "options": {
         "A": "Fruits",
         "B": "Eggs",
         "C": "Chips",
         "D": "Nuts"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = B"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "How many classes of food do we have?",
     "options": {
         "A": "4",
         "B": "6",
         "C": "7",
         "D": "5"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = B"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "An example of Protein is",
     "options": {
         "A": "Bread",
         "B": "Jam",
         "C": "Beans",
         "D": "Chocolate"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = C"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "What are energy giving foods?",
     "options": {
         "A": "Carbohydrates",
         "B": "Proteins",
         "C": "Vitamins",
         "D": "Calcium"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = A"
 },  

{ 

    "question": " Which of these is not a wild animal?",
     "options": {
         "A": "Lion",
         "B": "Leopard",
         "C": "Dog",
         "D": "Tiger"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = C"
 },  

 
{ 

    "question": "A nuclear family is made up of",
     "options": {
         "A": "Grandparents, parents and children",
         "B": "Uncles, grandparents and children",
         "C": "Uncles, parents and children",
         "D": "Parents and children"
     },
 
     "answer": "Answer = D"
    }
   

]